Guide to the Stanford University Poster Collection SC1030
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Posters
  - Neocolonialism in South America, Un-dated; 415; 20x26 inches (Box map case)
  - New Campus Cyclery, Un-dated; 530-24; 11 x 14 inches (Box A4)
  - New Directory now on sale at Business Office, Un-dated; 32; 14 x 23 inches (Box C1)
  - New Perspectives on the Reformation, 1965; 2013; 14 x 11 inches (Box A1)
  - New Stanford Stadium A Grand Opening Season September 16, 2006-. Reverse has instructions for card stunt using this item., 2008-002; 16 x 24 inches (Box C10)
  - New York Pro Musica, 1966; 202-19; 11 x 17 inches (Box A1)
  - NO MORE DISRUPTION. REASON MUST PREVAIL AT STANFORD. COALITION FOR AN ACADEMIC COMMUNITY [April 30, 1969], 527-04; 11 x 17 inches (Box C4)
  - No More Vietnams: No More Counter-insurgency Research. Join us at AEL [April 1969], 527-02; 14 x 22 inches (Box C4)
  - NO TO THE SIT-IN IS DEATH TO THE ISSUES [April 1969], 527-03; 14 x 22 inches (Box C4)
  - No! On the Briggs Initiative B.A.C.A.B.I., [1978]; 2008-013; 14 x 22 inches (Box C10)
    Came with the L. Timothy Portwood papers. The Briggs Initiative attemped to ban gays and lesbians from working in CA public schools.
  - Nomura Kyogen Company- Japanese Classical Comedy, 1968; 903-2; 11 x 14 inches (Box A4)
  - Norman Maclean "Putting Together Sky, Fire, and Words" at Annenberg Auditorium, 2015-001; 11 x 17 inches (Box A6)
  - Notable Campus Canines (with a nod to cats) Stories from the Stanford University Archives. Munger Rotunda Green Library January 19--March 29, 2009. [exhibit poster], 2010-018; 24.5 x 17.5 inches (Box C10)
  - "Now I Lay Me Down to Sleep", 1949; 511-23; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - Now Showing: Africa Open for Business. [documentary by Carol Pineau]. Wednesday, April 19, 2006-, 2010-006; 11 x 17 inches (Box A5)
  - "Of Mice and Men", 1948; 511-16; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - On the Bridge at the Border: Migrants and Immigrants. Arturo Islas, 1990; 908-02; 11 x 14 inches (Box A4)
  - "Once Upon a Mattress" Tryouts, Un-dated; 508-9; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - one more reason to drive less. Learn more at transporation.stanford.edu/CoralReefs. Every trip counts. Stanford University Parking & Transportation Services, 2009; 39820; 19 x 11.5 inches (Box C10)
  - One-Acts, 1949; 513-30; 22 x 28 inches (Box D2)
  - Opera and Vocal Concert / Hansel und Gretel conducted by Mr. Arthur Fickenscher. Preceding opera Grand Vocal Concert. Assembly Hall Stanford University, Thursday October 10 [could be 1901- or 1907], 524-33; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
    Has stamp on reverse "STANFORD UNIVERSITY PRESS SAMPLE". This matches stamp from poster dated 1900.
  - Organ and Choral Music, 1965; 202-10; 11 x 19 inches (Box A1)
  - Organ Recital, 1965; 202-12; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A1)
  - Organizing Nonviolence, 1966; 331; 14x22 inches (Box C1)
  - "Othello", Un-dated; 507-7; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - "Othello", 1948; 511-18; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - Our Day in Court, 1968; 905-49; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box not specified)
  - OUR DAY IN COURT. [demonstration at arraignment of persons arrested in "Battle of Lytton Plaza" organized by Stanford SDS, Nov. 1968], 905-49; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A3)
  - Paintings by Edward M. Farmer a retrospective exhibition October 28 to November 15 Stanford University Art Gallery, 1964 or 1965; 2003-002 (Box C4)
    Removed from bio file (1/29/2003-)
  - Palo Alto Community Players- "Billeted", Un-dated; 903-3; 11 x 14 inches (Box A4)
  - Panel Discussion, 1966; 15; 22 x 14 inches (Box C1)
  - Panel Discussion: Beyond SES: A Vision of Radical and Ducation, 1969; 23; 22 x 14 inches (Box C1)
  - Papua New Guinea Sculpture Garden Opening Celebration Week May 28--June 1 [1996], 2010-020; 11 x 17 inches (Box GW403)
  - Past Dependencies. The Stanford Presidential Symposium on: the Social Sciences, law, and the Humanities. November 5-6 [1999], 2003-035; 14 x 22.5 inches (Box C4)
  - Paul Berg Symposium San Francisco 28-30 June 1991, 2008-009; 20 x 26 inches (Box D1)
  - Paul M. Latz. Assembly 24th District. Vietnam: Withdraw trops, negotiate;--Fight Poverty! Monday May 2 [1966] "Sponsored by SCPV" written in on poster., 905-38; 10 x 14 inches (Box B2)
  - Paul Salinas Presents: Chicanindio Poetics--La Loma to Lacandon, 1994; 905-88; 17.5x22 inches (Box C3)
  - Peace Corps Goes to Paradise, 1966; 333; 11x14 inches (Box A2)
  - Peace Corps Movies, Un-dated; 905-30; 14 x 22 inches (Box not specified)
  - Peer Gynt, Un-dated; 400; 11 x 14 inches (Box A2)
  - "Peking and the New Left", 1969; 368; 8 1/2x 11 inches (Box A2)
  - Perry Dilley's Puppets, 1931; 905-4; 14 x 11 inches (Box A4)
  - "Peter Grimes", 1948; 511-14; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1965; 10; 9 x 12 inches (Box A1)
  - Photographs--Eadweard Muybridge, 1965; 13; 19x15 (Box C1)
  - Picture Jasper Ridge, a performance hike by Ann Carlson, 2012 Mar 9-11; 2015-003; 11 x 17 inches (Box A6)
    Stanford Institute for Creativity and the Arts (SiCa); Jasper Ridge Biological Preserve (Calif.); Stanford University. Department of Drama
  - "Pierre of the Plains", Un-dated; 504-2; 14 x 21 inches (Box C7)
  - "Pillars of Society", Un-dated; 5049; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - PKWTNOPrV, 1903-; 530-2; 13 x 20 inches (Box C7)
  - PLEASE COME--THE ELECTORAL WAKE. A candle-light procession of mourning chants and celebration. Gather on the Palm Drive Oval with Joan Baez and other communal folk to stroll to the polls. Tuesday Nov. 5 [1968] 7 p.m., 905-48; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A3)
    text on reverse
  - Poetry Reading, 1965; 324; 14x22 inches (Box C1)
  - Poetry Reading, 1965; 328; 14x22 inches (Box C1)
  - Poetry Reading--James Wright, 1965; 414; 14x22 inches (Box C2)
  - Poetry Reading by William Dickey, 1965; 325; 14x22 inches (Box C1)
  - Poetry Reading: Robert Creeley, Un-dated; 411; 14x22 inches (Box C2)
  - Political Arrests, 1968; 905-47; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box not specified)
  - POLITICAL ARRESTS / NOT IN NAZI GERMANY, NOT IN THE SOVIETY UNION, BUT RIGHT HERE IN PALO ALTO [followed by text and announcement of a march from campus to the PA Police Station, Nov. 1968], 905-47; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A3)
  - Political Development in the Middle East, 1968; 340; 14x22 inches (Box C1)
  - "Polly with a Past", Un-dated; 513-47; 14 x 20 inches (Box C7)
  - Polynesian Life in a Tropical Atoll, Un-dated; 407; 9x12 inches (Box C2)
  - Pompeii to Palo Alto: A Century of Stanford Archaeology. A Stanford Centennial Exhibit at Meyer Library. Sponsored by the Office of Campus Archaeology., 1991; 201-15; 10.75 x 17 inches (Box A1)
  - Posada En Stanford, 1989; 532-02; 11x17 inches (Box A2)
  - Prevent four years of "Law & Order" / Help elect HUMPREY CRANSTON / Room 271--Tresidder Union, Wed. Oct. 2nd [1968], 905-43; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A3)
  - Prevent Four Years of Law and Order, 1968; 905-43; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box not specified)
  - "Priates of Penzance", 1902-; 513-6; 14 x 20 inches (Box C6)
  - Program in Feminist Studies at Stanford 1988-89 Courses., 21402; 17 x 25 inches (Box D2)
  - Program in Feminist Studies at Stanford. 1989-90 Courses, 21403; 17 x 25 inches (Box D2)
  - Promote Peace in our Cities, 1968; 905-60; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box A4)
  - Proposition 187: Will It Save Our State? A Panel Discussion, Un-dated; 526-07; 11x17 inches (Box C7)
  - Prospective on Vietnam, Un-dated; 127; 11 x 17 inches (Box A1)
  - Puppet Studio Theatre presents The Unicorn of Now and Ever. Directed by Nancy H. Cole. Cubberley Theater, Palo Alto. [1969 or 1980], 2006-044; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - Quad, 1968; 514-7; 12 x 18 inches (Box C7)
  - Quad, circa 1975; 514-16; 17 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - Quad, circa 1975; 514-17; 17 x 22 inches (Box not specified)
  - Queer Studies Colloquium (FEMST 106/206), 2012 Fall; 2015-007; 11 x 17 inches (Box A6)
    Stanford University. Feminist Studies Program
  - Queerland, Stanford. Hand-letterd sign from protest at Gov. Wilson's talk during Centennial event, October 1991. "Loud, proud and in your face" "Pete marches to the beat of Sheldon and his Bible-banging brigade", 20 x 30 in; 906-01 (Box not specified)
  - "R.U.R.", Un-dated; 513-57; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - Race, Inequality, and Incarceration. An intellectual summit... The Bechtel Conference Center, April 11, 2007 [Presented by] The Center for Comparative Studies in Race and Ethnicity, The Institute for Research in the Social Sciences (& others), 2007-012; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
    picked up on campus
  - Raiders of the Lost Axe, 1983; 509-14; 22.5 x 17.5 inches (Box D2)
  - Ram's Head Presents Big Game Gaieties of 1949. [includes program and credits, with an over-print in red of theatrical masks and pennant with the letter S.], 39816; 20 x 15 inches (Box B3)
  - Ram's Head presents Cabaret. Memorial Auditorium April 14, 15, 20, 21, 22 [2006-], 2006-009; 13 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - Ram's Head presents Gaieties 2009 / Apocalypse Cal The End is Near Nov 18, 19, 20, 2009-023; 18 x 24 inches (Box C10)
  - Ram's Head Presents The Original Winter One Acts 2010-. Play 2 / The Fisherman / Top of Show, 2010-001; 11.5 x 17.5 inches (Box B3)
  - Ram's Head Theatrical Society Presents Gaieties 2007 / Herbert Hoover and the Order of the Bearclaw, 2007-017; 18x24 inches (Box C4)
  - Ram's Head Theatrical Society Presents Gaieties 2010- The Last Temptation of CAL. Memorial Auditorium November 17, 18, 19, 2010-019; 18 x 24.5 inches (Box C10)
  - Ram's Head Theatrical Society presents West Side Story, Memorial Auditorium, April 11-12, 17-19, 2003-, 2006-062; 17 x 22 inches (Box C4)
  - Rastafari and the Black Woman [a film]. Monday November 5 [1984] Toyon Lounge. Sponsored by the Office of Residential Education., 2006-048; 8.5 x 14 inches (Box B2)
  - Raul Salinas Presents: Chicanindio Poetics- La Loma to Lacandon. 1994 Bay Area Tour., 905-88; 17.5 x 22.5 inches (Box not specified)
  - " 'Ray, 'Ray, Rover Boys!", 1926; 5081; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - Realism in Film, 1964; 9; 12 x 19 in (Box B4)
  - Redeem the time, redeem the dream. ASH WED '68. Feb. 28, 7:30p.m. MEM CHU, 1968; 905-40; 8.5 X 11 inches (Box A3)
  - Refiguring Culture: Cinema & Society in Contemporary Berl inches (Film series and symposium)., circa 1987; 2131; 17 x 11 inches (Box not specified)
    German Studies, Dept. of
  - Reflections: Women and Self-Images. Jing Lyman Lectures / Spring 1989, 216-01; 10x20 inches (Box B1)
    IRWG -- Jing Lyman Lectures
  - Reflections on the American Condition: A Celebration of the Career of David M. kennedy, March 2008, 2008-003; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - Rehearsal of "Every Man in his Humour", 1905-; 530-3; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box A4)
  - Religion of a Sensible American, The, 1911; 108; 14 x 22 inches (Box C1)
  - Representative John Conyers, 1969; 366; 14 x 22 inches (Box C2)
  - Republican Rally, 1900; 905-18; 14 x 21 inches (Box not specified)
  - Research Institute for Comparative Studies in Race and Ethnicity. Models for Diversity the University's Role in Shaping an Inclusive Society. March 5-6, 1999, 2002-012; 11 x 17 inches (Box B1)
  - Rethinking Science & Civilization. The Ideologies, Disciplines, and Rhetorics of World History. May 21-23, 1999. In Celebration of the 50th Anniversary of Humanities and Sciences at Stanford., 2003-013; 11 x 17 inches (Box A2)
  - Reverend Kirby Hensley Reading, 1969; 378; 14 x 22 inches (Box C2)
  - "Richard III", Nov. 6-8, 1947; 511-11; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - "Right Your Are", Un-dated; 513-46; 14 x 20 inches (Box C7)
  - Roger Chartier, Cultural Historian. Presidential and Endowed Lectures in the Humanities and Arts. October 16-17, 2000, 2003-021; 14 x 14 inches (Box B1)
  - "Romeo and Juliet", 1949; 511-24; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - Rostand's "Cyrano de Bergerac", 1948; 511-12; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - Rubbings of Mayan Reliefs by Merle Greene. September 27- October 27, 1968, 203-11; 13 x 20 inches (Box B1)
  - Rugby--All Star Interscholastic Rugby, 1913; 804-1; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Rugby--Benefit Game, Un-dated; 804-3; 11x14 inches (Box A4)
  - Rugby--Freshmen vs Lowell High School, Un-dated; 804-6; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Rugby--Freshmen vs Santa Cruz, Un-dated; 804-5; 8 1/2x 11 inches (Box A4)
  - Rugby--Stanford vs California, Un-dated; 804-2; 14x22 inches (Box map case)
  - Rugby--Varsity vs Nevada, Un-dated; 804-7; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - Rugby--Varsity vs University of Nevada, Un-dated; 804-4; 14x22 inches (Box C8)
  - "Rutherford and ...?", Un-dated; 513-52; 11 x 23 inches (Box C7)
    Ripped in half, and thus the end of the title is not visible.
  - S.F. Mime Troupe- "A Minstrel Show", 1966; 903-1; 20 x 14 inches (Box C10)
  - S.F. Newsreel. Columbia Revolt / An impassioned & partisan account of last spring's insurrection at Columbia University....Memorial Auditorium Wed. Oct. 9 [1968], 905-61; 10.5 x 15 inches (Box B2)
    "S.F. Newsreel" with graphic is printed; other information is hand-written.
  - Salsa Specular, Un-dated; 519-09; 11x17 inches (Box A2)
  - Samson Raphaelsons' New Comedy: "Jason", June 10-12, 1948; 511-15; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - San Francisco Bay: Fill It and Subdivide IT..., 1969; 375; 14x22 inches (Box C2)
  - SASA World Cup '07. April 22, 2007. Roble Field. [part of Africa Week 2007], 2010-008; 11 x 17 inches (Box A5)
  - School of Medicine--Violence, 1968; 209-1; 11 x 17 inches (Box A1)
    Medicine, School of
  - SCIRE and SWOPSI present films of Repression Resistance and Rebellion Mondays at 7:30 [1976], 2006-034; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - Scrap of Paper, 1903-; 107; 14 x 11 inches (Box A1)
  - Sequoia, 1957; 514-6; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - Settlement Work in connection with Social Service, An Address by Harry F. Ward., Un-dated; 387; 11x14 inches (Box A2)
  - Seventeenth Annual Ernest Galarza Commemorative Lecture, Dolores Huerta, May 17, 2002, 2002-001; 28 x 36 inches (Box mc--bsmt)
  - Sex and the Invisible Curriculum, Un-dated; 413; 14x22 inches (Box C2)
  - Sex Education in Public Schools, 1969; 363; 14x22 inches (Box C2)
  - "She Got Out" and "Play", 1969; 5086; 11 x 17 inches (Box C6)
  - "Shootki", June 26-28, 1947; 511-9; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - "Shvanda", 1949; 511-22; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - Sigma Alpha Iota, Gamma Beta chapter presents American Musicale chamber music by Traditional & Contemporary American Composers Thursday 22 February [1968], 524-26; 11 x 14 inches (Box A3)
  - Simps Shows!, 24-25 May [?]; 2015-009; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A6)
    Stanford Improvisers (SImps)
  - Sir Frank Kermode Literary Critic The Levinthal Distinguished Visitor Speaking on the Occasion of the Dedication of the Elliott and Rhoda Levinthal Hall. Stanford Humanities Center. Nov. 14, 2001., 2007-002; 14.5 x 24.5 inches (Box C4)
  - Sir. John Bagot Glubb, 1968; 354; 14 x 22 inches (Box C1)
  - "Six Characters in Search of an Author", 1951; 511-29; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - Ski Club Spring Carnival, 1969; 530-10; 14 x 22 inches (Box C7)
  - SLAC--Science in Society, 1968; 2101; 14 x 22 inches (Box C1)
    SLAC
  - "Snapshots of Stanford Life", 1910; 514-14; 11 x 14 inches (Box A4)
  - "Snicket is Coming", 2013 Oct 9; 2015-004; 11 x 14 inches (Box A6)
  - Socialism in Britian, 1969; 379; 14x22 inches (Box C2)
  - Sokel Speaking on Brecht, 1966; 115; 8.5 x 14 inches (Box A1)
  - Solidarity Rally for Mexican Students. Friday 8 p. m. Lytton Plaza. Speakers Andres Chavez, Aaron Manganiello, a Black Panther, others, 1968; 905-41; 8.5 x 14 inches (Box B2)
    Includes text on front and back.
  - Some Preliminary Second Thoughts on the Presidency, 1968; 357; 14x22 inches (Box C2)
  - Song Recital by Father McLouflin, 1901-; 309; 11x14 inches (Box A6)
  - Song Recital, given by: Miss Millie Flynn, Miss May Ferrel, Mrs. J. Newton Tharp, Un-dated; 524-35; 14x22 inches (Box C3)
  - Soph-Frosh tie-up between classes of 1923 and 1924: "The last and only warning of the '23 class to the unorganized rabble of the frosh. Broadening his mind. Never Kick a Frosh in the Face; Nature Provided a Better Place." In the shape of a coffin, with a black border., 2010-009; 38 x 22 inches (Box mc--bsmt)
  - Sophomore Comedy: The Rivals, 1/27/1905-; 501-74; 27 x 12 inches (Box D2)
  - Sophomore Play: "Seven-Twenty-Eight", 1909; 501-24; 25x21 inches (Box D2)
  - Sotere Torregian, 1968; 356; 14 x 22 inches (Box C2)
  - Spoken Word Collective Fall Show. Soapbox...belligerence on a budget...Dec. 4 [2009], 2009-024; 11 x 17 inches (Box A5)
  - Spring 2009 Research Seminar Anthro 337A--FrenGen 367. Violence, the Sacred and Rights of the Dead. Ewa Domanska, Department of Anthropology, 39814; 12 x 16.5 inches (Box B3)
  - SST--Boom or Bust, 1969; 905-74; 14 x 22 inches (Box C9)
  - Stadium Spectacular Stanford Centennial, 1991; 90702; 22x19.25 inches (Box C10)
    One copy is autographed yb the performers
  - Stanford (in the manner of the New Yorker cover); artist Sue Cashell., Un-dated; 905-84; 18 x 26 inches (Box not specified)
    Signed by the artist
  - Stanford 43rd Annual Powwow, 2014 May 9-11; 2015-024; 17 x 22 inches (Box C11)
  - Stanford 1936 Season--Stanford Pavilion [basketball schedule], 2008-012; 14 x 22 inches (Box not specified)
    Printed on stiff board which is now brittle; 2 corners damaged
  - Stanford 1977 Football Play By Play Action KSFO/560 Radio. Graphic of Hoover Tower, b/w of color print of Ernie Nevers by Lowell Herrero, several photos., 2007-005; 19 x 25 inches (Box D1)
  - Stanford 1997-1998 Calendar, 37; 25 x 37 inches (Box map case)
    Oct.--June with ads, academic calendar, athletic schedule, phone numbers
    Calendars.
  - Stanford 2013-2014 Calendar, Accession ARCH-2017-029 (Box Tube 1)
  - Stanford African Students Association Africa Week 2002. Africa on the Move. [Features painting by Eto Otitigbe.], 2002 May 12-18; 2002-017; 13 x 23 inches (Box C3)
    Poster is heavily laminated
  - Stanford African Students Association presents Affrica Night 2007 Saturday, April 28, 2007, 2010-007; 11 x 17 inches (Box A5)
  - Stanford American Indian Organization 20th Anniversary 1970-1990., 2004-001; 22.5 x 17 inches (Box C4)
    Includes short history and calendar of events in October 1990.
    Student organizations
  - Stanford Baseball [schedule] 2004. Signed by team members, 2007-001; 18 x 24 inches (Box C4)
    2/13/07 being flatted in GW403
  - Stanford Bookstore Spring Author Series. Lester Brown at Branner Hall, April 6. Inscribed to Kennall Jackson and signed by Brown, 1990; 2005-006; 28 x 22 inches (Box D1)
  - Stanford Cares: A Community Response. Aids Memorial Service Names Project & Benefit Concert. Thursday, February 18, 1988, 2006-047; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - Stanford Center for Buddhist Studies Spring Lecture Series "In the Shadow of the Bamiyan Buddhas: Recovering Afghanistan's Buddhist Past" Paul Harrison Thursday, May 24, 2007., 2007-013; 11 x 17 inches (Box B2)
  - Stanford Choral Society, Un-dated; 524-40; 14 x 20 inches (Box not specified)
  - Stanford Committee for Biafran/Nigerian Relief, 1969; 905-73 (Box C9)
  - Stanford Community and SES, 1969; 20; 22 x 14 inches (Box C1)
  - Stanford Conservation Group- "The Grand Canyon", 1968; 5232; 10 x 14 inches (Box A4)
  - Stanford Conservation Group- "The Redwoods", 1968; 5231; 9 1/2 x 14 inches (Box A4)
  - Stanford Conservation Group- Green Foothills, 1967; 5234; 8 1/2 x 14 inches (Box not specified)
  - Stanford Conservation Group- Population and Environment: The Decision We Must Make, 1969; 5233; 14 x 22 inches (Box C8)
  - Stanford Department of Music 1966-67 Subscription Series, 202-21; 14 x 22 inches (Box C1)
  - Stanford Drama Dept. presents Three Penny Opera. February 18-20, 25-27 Memorial Auditorium [no year noted], 2006-052; 14.5 x 22 inches (Box C4)
  - Stanford Drama Presents Timberlake Wertenbaker's OUR COUNTRY'S GOOD. directed by Amy Freed & Clara Murphy. May 26, 27, 28, 29--Nitery Theater, 2010-; 2010-014; 17.5 x 12 inches (Box B3)
  - Stanford East European Faculty, 1969; 119; 8.5 x 11 inches (Box A1)
  - Stanford Employee's Association Meeting, 1968; 905-8; 14 x 22 inches (Box C9)
  - Stanford Employee's Association Meeting, 1968; 905-10; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box A4)
  - Stanford Employee's Association Meeting, 1968; 905-11; 14 x 22 inches (Box C9)
  - Stanford Fall Sports Schedule, 2012; 2015-020; 12 x 18 inches (Box B4)
  - Stanford Film Society, 1957; 530-4; 9 1/2 x 12 inches (Box A4)
  - Stanford George Washington Memorial Association Benefit Recital. Miss Grace Barstoe, violinist, Miss Jannie Janes, accompanist. University Chapel Friday Evening, November 4 [could be 1904 or 1910], 524-36; 14 x 11 inches (Box A3)
  - Stanford Glee and Varsity Mandolin Clubs: Sixth Annual Holiday Hour, 1901-; 524-9; 14x22 inches (Box C3)
  - Stanford Glee and Varsity Mandolin Clubs: Sixth Annual Holiday Hour, 1902-; 524-10; 14x22 inches (Box C3)
  - Stanford Humanities Center. The 2002 Harry Camp Memorial Lectures given by Anthony Sampson. Mandela Reconciliation and Shakespeare. January 22, 2002, 2007-004; 12.25 x 23.25 inches (Box C4)
  - Stanford in New York City (SiNYC), 2015 Jan 25; 2015-017; 11 x 17 inches (Box A6)
  - Stanford in Washington, 1965; 530-18; 14 x 22 inches (Box C8)
  - Stanford Japanese American Reunion, September 30-October 1, 1993; 703; 11x17 (Box A2)
  - Stanford Law School and the Stanford Humanities Center present "The Second Amendment: History, Evidence, and the Constitution" April 20-21, 2001, 2003-029; 11 x 17 inches (Box A2)
  - Stanford Libraries--An Announcement of Historical Interest, 1960; 2011; 26 x 13 inches (Box D2)
  - Stanford Libraries--An Exhibition of Recently Acquired Books, Un-dated; 20114; 11 x 19 inches (Box A1)
  - Stanford Libraries--D. H. Lawrence: An Exhibition with a Lecture by Mark Schorer, 1968; 20111; 15 x 24 inches (Box C1)
  - Stanford Libraries--Masks of Innocence in the 1890s, a Lecture by John Felstiner, 1966; 2016; 17 x 11 inches (Box A1)
  - Stanford Libraries--Meyer Library Tours, 1968; 20110; 14 x 22 inches (Box C1)
    Libraries
  - Stanford Libraries--Stanford History Series, 1968; 2019; 14 x 22 inches (Box C1)
  - Stanford Lively Arts presents "The Limon Centenary: Limon Dance Company with the Stanford Symphony Orchestra", 39928; 2009-003; 11 x 17 inches (Box C6)
  - Stanford Musical Clubs, Un-dated; 524-39; 22 x 28 inches (Box not specified)
  - Stanford Opera Theatre, 1969; 524-32; 14 x 22 inches (Box not specified)
  - Stanford Players and Department of Music Present Two American Folk Operas: "The Jumping Frog of Calaveras County" and "The Devil and Daniel Webster", 1951; 511-27; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - Stanford Players and Department of Music Present Two American Operas" The Jumping Frog of Calaveras County" and "The Devil and Daniel Webster", 1951; 511-28; 14 x 22 inches (Box C6)
  - Stanford Players Summer Season: "Cyrano de Bergerac", "The Cretan Woman", "Camino Real", "Lysistrata"., Un-dated; 511-46; 14 x 22 inches (Box C5)
  - Stanford Players' 1957-58 Season, 511-38; 8 1/2 x 11 inches (Box A3)
  - Stanford Population and Environment Forum- Death on the Bay Shore, 1969; 9042; 14 x 22 inches (Box C9)
  - Stanford Population and Environment Forum- Genocide: Implications of Birth Control Policy?, 1969; 9043; 14 x 22 inches (Box C9)
  - Stanford Population and Environment Forum- Proposals for Legislative Action, 1968; 9041; 14 x 22 inches (Box C9)
  - Stanford Population andd Environment Forum- Population vs. Planet Earth, 1969; 9044; 14 x 22 inches (Box C9)
  - Stanford Presidential Lectures and Symposia in the Humanities and Arts. Cristo and Jeanne-Claude; Peter Eisenman; Helen Cixous; Harold Bloom, 1998; 418; 6.25x16 inches (Box A1)
    Non-Stanford Speakers-Presidential Lectures
  - Stanford Presidential Lectures and Symposia in the Humanities and Arts. October--November 1998. Henry Louis Gates, Jr; Stephen Jay Gould; Karl Heinz Bohrer; Wole Soyinka., 420; 7 x 20.5 inches (Box B1)
    Presidential Lectures